http://www.heidts.com/privacy-policy/

(800) 841-8188
Welcome, guest!
Login
Cart(0)
Last Modified: 8/25/2014
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE OR SUBMITTING ANY INFORMATION, PARTICULARLY PERSONAL INFORMATION, THROUGH THE SITE.  BY USING THE SITE, YOU ARE AGREEING TO THESE PRIVACY TERMS, INCLUDING OUR COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE, DO NOT USE THE SITE.
1. Our Commitment To Privacy
Heidts is committed to respecting the privacy and security of the personal information of every individual who uses our website, www.heidts.com (which we refer to in this Privacy Policy as the “site”, which term also refers to any content, functionality and services offered on or through the site).  This Privacy Policy outlines the information we will collect and how we will use that information, so that you may be informed about how we use your personal information and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and change, your information.
The site is owned by Heidts Automotive LLC (who we refer to, together with our affiliates, as “us”, “we” or “our”).
2.  Changes To Our Privacy Policy
Because of changes in Internet technology and practices, this Privacy Policy, and our security and other policies, may change from time to time.  Please consult this portion of the site for important changes to the Privacy Policy as they occur.  By using the site after we post any changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to accept those changes, whether or not you have reviewed them, and such acceptance will be deemed legally conclusive.
3.  How We May Collect and Use Non-Personally Identifiable Information
General.  You can visit most of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.  Like most websites, we automatically collect certain information as you browse our site, but the data we collect in this manner is limited to “browsing data” that is not used to personally identify you.  Examples of this type of information include the IP address of the computer used when accessing the site, information about your operating system and computer environment, the frequency of your use of the site, and your use of any hyperlinks available on the site.  We and our service providers, agents and advisors may process and use this data for purposes such as making sure the site works properly, assessing patterns of use, making improvements to the quality of the site and planning and evaluating marketing and communications initiatives.
Cookies.  When you view the site, we might store some information on your computer in the form of a “cookie” or similar file.  “Cookies” are small text files that either are used for the duration of a session (‘session cookies’), or are saved on a user’s hard drive in order to identify that user the next time he/she logs on to the site (‘persistent cookies’).  We may use ‘session cookies’ to identify registered users logging in to the site.  These cookies are deleted from the component’s server soon after the session ends and are not collected or saved.
We use ‘persistent cookies’ to recognize you when you return to the site, to recognize your password if you have clicked on the “save password” check box on login, and to analyze visitor behavior.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. You can usually change your browser to prevent that, such as by having your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or by choosing to turn off all cookies.  This can be done through your web browser settings. Because each browser is different, you should look at your browser’s “Help” menu to learn how to modify your cookie settings.  If you do disable cookies from your browser you may not be able to access certain sections of the site and this may make your experiences on the site less efficient.
Pixel Tags.  We may also use pixel tags, which are tiny graphic images, to help us analyze your online behavior.  Pixel tags also will allow us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.
We may use pixel tags to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with our web site and our services.  We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring web site addresses.
4.  How We May Collect and Use Personally Identifiable Information
“Personally identifiable information” (also referred to as “personal information”) is information that can be used to individually identify you, such as your name, address, email address and phone number.  The site does not automatically collect personally identifiable information, and we will only collect such information if you voluntarily provide it to us.
We may obtain personally identifiable information from the following sources:
Email Communications. We may collect information that we receive from you when you contact us through the “Contact Us” link on the site.  This information may include your name, email address, address, phone number, and any other information you voluntarily include with your correspondence. If you have provided us with any information through the “Contact Us” link, and believe it is incorrect or has been changed since you provided it, or if you would like us to remove any personal information from our records, you should contact us again via the “Contact Us” link.
Account Information.  If you register to use the site, you will be required to submit certain information, such as your name and email address.  We will retain this information in our records relating to the site. We may use the email address you enter on the site to send you updates, and to contact you regarding any content you submit to the site[, including, for example, to let you know whether any content that you have submitted will be posted to the site] (see our Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms of Use”), available at Terms and Conditions of Use, for more information regarding submitting content to the site).  If you believe that any of this type of personal information collected by us is incorrect, or has been changed since your initial registration on the Site, you should let us know by using the “Contact Us” link, or updating your account information through the login pages.
Purchase Information.  When you use the site to make a purchase, even if you do not create an account we will need to collect certain information from you, including your name, shipping address, telephone number, email address, and your billing address and credit card information.
Content.  Subject to the Terms of Use, you can contribute to the site in a number of different ways.  We may store these contributions (“User Content”), display them to other users, and use them for purposes consistent with the purpose of the site.  Your posting of any User Content is entirely voluntary and is at your own risk.  We are not responsible for the information that you choose to include in your User Content, including any information that could be used to personally identify you. If you include personally identifiable information in any User Content that is made available on the site, it can be viewed and used by any person viewing the site, and therefore your inclusion of any personally-identifiable information in any User Content is solely at your discretion and your risk.  Also, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content will not be viewed by persons other than users of the site. For example, users of the site may share information available on the site with third parties, and we cannot control such activities.  Furthermore, you should be aware that even if we remove User Content, copies of it may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or may have been copied or stored by other users of the site.
Third Party Services.  We may allow you to access third party services, such as Facebook and Twitter, to share selected User Content with those services. Your sharing of User Content through such third-party services is subject to the privacy practices of those services.
The site may also serve third-party content that contains their own cookies or tracking technologies, which means that third parties may be able to (through cookies, web beacons, or other tracking technology) collect information about you when you use the site. We cannot control these technologies or how they may be used.
5.  How We May Use and Share Information Generally
How We May Use Information.  We may store, process and use the information about you that we collect through the site in order to:
Respond to your questions, comments, other feedback or requests for information;
Customize and/or personalize your communications and your shopping experience;
Communicate with you about your purchases, your account information or customer service matters;
Administer web site features;
Distribute marketing materials, promotions and surveys;
Compile statistical information about our users’ equipment, browsing actions and patterns; and
Learn how to improve our site, services and products.
How We May Share Information.  To enable us to more efficiently operate the site we may share your personal and other information with our affiliates and with selected third parties who are acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers, or providers.   These third party service providers will be provided only with such information as is necessary under the circumstances.  Information provided to third parties will be permitted to be used only for the purposes stipulated by us, and those third parties will be subject to confidentiality obligations.  We may also enhance or merge personally identifiable information with data obtained from third parties for any of the foregoing purposes.
Required Disclosures.  We may be required to disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect our or others’ rights, property or safety.  We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation.  Nothing in this Privacy Policy shall be deemed to prohibit us from disclosing your identity or information if we are required to do so or if we believe such action is appropriate under the circumstances described in this paragraph.
6.  Our Security Measures
In order to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of any personal information you provide to us, we have put into place standard physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.  When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server.  All credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be accessed only as stated above.
Unfortunately, no electronic data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, although we believe that we use reasonable measures to protect personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted or otherwise provided to us or received from us.  This is especially true for information that is transmitted via e-mail that is unprotected until it reaches our servers
7.  How to Manage Your Information
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us.  If you prefer not to receive information from us or would like to update or change your personal information or preferences, follow the instructions below.
Correcting, Modifying and Deleting Your Information. If you believe that any of your personal information collected by us is incorrect, or has been changed since your registration on the site, please contact us via e-mail at sales@heidts.com, explaining the correction or change and providing any relevant confirmation or reference number.
To modify or delete entirely your account information, you can log in to your account and update your profile.
Email Distributions.  To unsubscribe from our email distributions, you can follow the instructions in any email you receive.  You can also contact us via e-mail at sales@heidts.com.  Be sure to include your first and last name and account email address in the “message” box.
Direct Mail and Catalog Distributions.  If you would like your name and address removed from our direct mailing list or if you would like to update your mailing information, you can phone us at 1-800-841-8188 from 8am-6pm Central Standard Time or contact us via e-mail at sales@heidts.com.  Be sure to include your first and last name and mailing address in the “message” box.
Communications in Progress/Sales and Service Information.  Please note, if you have unsubscribed from any of our communications, due to production schedules, you may receive communications already in production.  Also, if you request that your registration information be deleted or if you unsubscribe from communications, we may maintain information about sales transactions or service inquiries for future service and record keeping purposes.
8.  A Special Notice about Children
This site is not intended for unsupervised use by persons under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under 13.
If you are under 18, you must have your parent/guardian’s permission to use this site and to place any orders, and you should not submit any personal information to us without such permission.
If parents believe their minor children have accessed this site and provided their personally identifiable information, please contact us at sales@heidts.com.
9.  Other Sites
The site may contain links to other websites with which we have no affiliation.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other websites.  Users are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy of any website linked to from the site.
10.  Transfer of Business Assets
We continue to develop our business and in doing so might choose to sell our business, or certain assets of our business, to a third party.  Both personal information and non-personally identifiable information would generally be part of the transferred assets transferred in such transactions.
11.  Questions and Feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy.  Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue by contacting us at sales@heidts.com.
12.  Third Party Hosting
We contract with a third party to maintain and host the site.  Therefore, any information you submit, including personal information, will be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by this third-party host.  The third party has agreed to implement technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use.
13. We cannot respond to “Do Not Track” Requests.
Currently, certain web browsers, including Firefox, Google Chrome, Internet Explorer and Safari, offer a “Do Not Track” (DNT) option. This option is intended to send a signal to websites visited by the user about the user’s DNT preference, if any set on the browser. We do not commit to responding to a browser’s DNT signals, because no common industry standards for DNT have been adopted by industry groups, technology companies, or regulators.
